cardboard-crack.com 2019-03-10

# Privacy Policy - Cardboard Crack

**General privacy policy for visitors of cardboard-crack.tumblr.com  
**

Cardboard Crack is dedicated to protecting the privacy of the visitors to cardboard-crack.tumblr.com. We have provided this privacy policy so you know how your information is used. 

We collect information based on your IP address, including your country of origin, the type of web browser you use, what search engines you may have used to find cardboard-crack.tumblr.com, or what site may have referred you. This information is used for tracking purposes only, and it is never provided to any other entities.

 **Cookies and 3rd party advertisements  
**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2Fprivacy_ads.html&t=YzBkNDcxYmNkMzRkOTRmY2JhMTUzZmM4NmM0NWE4ZTFiYTdlY2U1NCxUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D&p=&m=0).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.networkadvertising.org%2Fmanaging%2Fopt_out.asp&t=NDBhYjdmYTE3MjkzODM4MGQ5YjczZGUzODk4NjlkZjBlZmYzN2Y5NSxUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D&p=&m=0).

 **Privacy policy with regard to use e-mail contact**

When you submit an e-mail to site the site author or any other persons speaking on behalf of Cardboard Crack to request additional information about Cardboard Crack or its services, the information you provide is used solely as a means to provide you with that information. Your information is used only for responding to your request and is never provided to any other entities. 

**Privacy questions**

If you have any questions with relation to our privacy practices or the web site itself, feel free to contact me at cardboardcrack.mtg@gmail.com.
